她怎么样了
How is she?
打了几剂吗啡
In and out of the morphine drip.
我只知道她情况算稳定了
They got her stabilized is all I know.
进去看看吧
Go on in.
不了
No.
那就把你的屁股从墙上移开
Unfreeze your ass off that wall, then.
要么进去关心关心伤员 要么把心思放回案子上
Either pay your respects, or get your head back into this case.
- 去他的案子 - 去他的?
- Fuck this case. - Fuck it?
你现在算是怎样 放弃你小小的斗争?
Now you're just gonna, what, call off your little crusade?
你是这么想的吗 一次斗争?
Is that what you think it was? A crusade?
查Avon Barksdale不过是 我展示自己有多聪明...
Avon Barksdale was a way to show everyone how smart I was...
而局里又有多烂的方式 如此而已
And how fucked up the department is, that's all.
他们只想把Jimmy McNulty踢给你...
Just put Jimmy McNulty up on your shoulders...
让他困在小房间里团团转 借酒消愁
March him around the room, break out the keg.
他们压根没想抓Avon Barksdale 队长
It was never about Avon Barksdale, Lieutenant.
只不过想打发我
It was all about me.
你以为我不知道吗
You think I didn't know that?
你以为大家都不知道吗
You think we all didn't know?
听着
Listen,
这案子会继续查下去...
This case is gonna move forward...
有你没你都一样
With you or without you.
她因为这案子中的枪
This case got her shot.
我使劲的鼓动她
I put a battery up her ass
让她误以为这案子大有可为
And got her thinking this case meant something.
你知道吗
And you know what?
Burrell和Rawls这帮人 他们是对的
Burrell, Rawls, and them, they were right.
这案子屁都不是
This case means exactly shit.
你大张旗鼓地跑我这儿来的时候
I know it meant damn near nothing to me
我就知道这案子对我毫无意义
When you came in beating the drum.
但现在一个女警躺在病床上 一个出色的警察...
But now we got that woman in there, that good police...
只能它妈的通过一根管子呼吸 因为这案子对她意味着什么
Breathing through a fucking tube, because it meant something to her.
而把Kima弄成这样的凶手呢?
And the shooters who dropped Kima?
他们依然逍遥法外
They're still in the wind.
而无论是谁把那些杂种派到巷子里...
And whoever sent those motherfuckers into that alley...
他也一定要付出代价
He needs to get got, too.
所以你想的话
So you can stand there,
大可以满身酒气地站在这自怨自艾
Dripping with liquor-smell and self-pity if you got a mind to,
但这件案子...
But this case...
现在有了意义
It means something. Now.
火线重案组 第一季 第十二集 清理
The Wire S01E012 Cleaning Up
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"这儿才是我的地盘"  ---Wallace
你又呼过他们了吗
You hit them again?
我呼了他们一个早上 到现在还没回复
I been calling them all morning. They ain't hit me back yet.
该死 到中午我们就断货了
Damn, we gonna tap out by noon.
Poot 我们还有多少
Poot! What we got over there?
200支 大概吧
200, maybe.
狗屎
Shit.
这它妈的啥玩意
What the fuck is this?
你它妈的以为是什么 小子 这是鱼饲料
What the fuck you think, nigger? Fish food.
还给我
Give me my shit.
抬头
Heads up.
String
String.
我要你们的呼机
I need your pagers.
你们所有人的 整个小组
All of y'all, the whole crew.
还差谁的
Who else?
Sterling Cass 还有Manny
Sterling, Cass and Manny.
好的 去问他们要来
All right, go get them shits.
我现在怎么跟我女友聊电话
How am I gonna talk to my girl?
跟你的手聊吧 小子 他们就是你女友
Talk to your hand, nigger, that's the only girl you got.
不要再... 闪一边去
No more.... Get out of here.
离这儿远点 伙计
Just get the fuck out of here, man.
不要再用呼机
No more pagers.
拉客的 望风的 都不许再用 懂吗
Touts, lookouts, off the air, all right?
除了你和Bodie 谁都不能用这些手机...
Nobody gonna use these cell phones except for you and Bodie...
你们也不能用它乱说话 懂吗
And y'all don't say shit on these, you understand me?
我们有号码 且仅限于我们几个使用
We got the numbers and we the only niggers that need them.
别把号码告诉你老妈 你女友 或其他任何人
Not your moms, not your girl, nobody.
明白吗
You feel me?
用这些手机安排会面
You use these phones to set up a meet,
见了面...
Go to that meet...
再慢慢谈 结束
And talk face to face, period.
这么说不用公共电话了?
So no more pay phones?
你聋了吗 我说了别打电话
You deaf? I said no phones.
那我怎么联系你们
How I'm gonna reach y'all?
好吧 最上面那个号码是要新货的...
All right, top number's for re-ups...
第二个是找打手的
Second number's for muscle.
要找我时 用第三个号码
You need me, hit me on the third number.
记住后 把这张纸处理了
Learn them shits, then throw that shit away.
你在高层公寓区那边也这么干吗
You doing this in the towers, too?
在所有地方都这么干 呼机 公共电话都不要再用
Doing it everywhere. Pagers, pay phones is dead.
- 明白吗 - 明白
- All right? - Yeah.
String
String.
我们要些新货 到中午就要断货了
We need some re-up, man, we gonna tap out by noon.
哪来的新货 你这家伙还没听说吗
Re-up from where? You niggers ain't heard?
缉毒警端掉了老窝
Knockos took the main stash.
你它妈的以为我们为什么要改规矩?
Why the fuck you think we changing up?
它妈的闪一边去 小鬼
Back the fuck up, young'un.
这些不是你该看的
These shits ain't for you.
好了
All right.
别动 就这样
Cool. There you go.
这就行了 好
There we go. All right.
纠正视力的礼物
The gift of corrected vision.
警局赠送
Compliments of the BPD.
亦可理解为"你们都聚精会神地看着我"
该死 你们都在焦点上了
Dang, y'all are focused.
哪个男人不会呢?
What man wouldn't be?
几天来他们一直在清理通话线路
They been cleaning us for the past few days.
昨晚他们处理掉最后一条
Last night they burned us all the way.
我就知道 我它妈的早知道
I knew it. I fucking knew it.
我对天发誓 我就是那帮混蛋肚里的蛔虫
I swear to God, I'm in this motherfucker's head.
从早上开始就没一条信息了
Not a message since early morning.
妈的 我甚至得把Prez派出去
Shit, I even had to cut Prez loose.
- 让他去Annapolis - 去干嘛
- Send his ass on down to Annapolis. - For what?
州竞选财务报告 这儿的我都查过了
State campaign finance reports. I checked all the stuff here.
不过我感觉Barksdale的钱"会走路"
But I got the feeling Barksdale's money has legs.
该死
Shit.
我们费尽心机建立这该死的监听线
All the work we did to get up on this fucking wire.
你不可能指望打击了他们 他们还乖乖呆瓮里
You don't hit these guys and expect them to stay in the pocket.
况且 他们知道自己放倒了个警察
Plus, they know they dropped a police.
那我们也得变招了
Then we need to change up, too.
过来
Come on.
Shardene
Shardene!
亲爱的 这位是McNulty侦探 我们的同事
Honey, this is Detective McNulty, who's working with us.
她在Orlando酒吧上班 不时给我们提供些帮助
She works at Orlando's, helping us out there from time to time.
而且现在我想她能把声音跟相貌对上了
And now I think that she can see well enough to match faces to voices.
Lester 听着 我不想骗你
Lester, look, I'm not gonna lie to you.
干这档事我很害怕
I'm scared of this shit.
虽然如此 我肯定 你时机一到就会勇往直前
Time comes, though, I know you gonna step up.
我们得让Pearlman批准她携带窃听器
We're gonna need Pearlman to approve her wearing a wire.
- 我能来杯咖啡吗 - 你想加点什么
- Can I get a cup of coffee? - What do you take in it?
我来吧 加一点奶油 对吧
I'll get it. A little cream, right?
那帮混账缉毒警把我抄了个干净
Those knockos motherfuckers cleaned my shit out.
你能找到新货和资金
You can replace product and currency.
是啊 他说得对 我们得关注当前问题
Yeah, he right. We gotta focus on what's real, here.
所有这些烂事就是当前问题 所有这些
All of this shit is real. All of it!
警察想把我抓进去
They wanna put me in a box.
听着 我认为当务之急是评估现状
Listen, I think what's important is to take stock.
自己想想现在还有什么能威胁到你
Ask yourself what's out there that can still hurt you.
你的软肋在哪
Where are you weak?
屁股还有哪里要擦干净
Where you need to clean up?
想想清楚
Think it through.
就从Orlando开始吧 如果他已经招供了
Start with Orlando, if Orlando rolled.
他至少会把俱乐部的情况供出来
You know he talked about the club, at least.
那个废物也就只能说点俱乐部的事
That punk-ass nigger ain't talk about shit else but the club.
他就知道这么多 没参与我们的活动
That's all he knew about. He wasn't rolling with us.
我们一直没让他染指
We kept him on the outside.
好吧 那你就放弃这个俱乐部
Alright, so you walk away from the club.
你名字不在执照上 也不是所有者之一
You're not on the license, you're not a listed owner.
他们就不能把你跟俱乐部联系起来
They can't make a connect.
这破事啥时开始的
When did this shit start up?
大约在你侄子打赢官司的时候
About the time that your nephew beat that charge.
之后 警察发现那个证人
After, maybe when they found that witness
被爆头了 那破事见了报
With the lead in his dome the shit hit the newspapers.
但大概就在那个时候 警察跟我们杠上了
But around that time, the cops was on our shit.
那个保安
The security guard,
曾指证D'Angelo的那个
The one whose testimony sprung D'Angelo--
- Nakeisha Lyles? - 对
- Nakeisha Lyles? - Yeah.
那个暴眼婊子 不过我们不是把她收买了吗
Bug-eyed ass bitch. But we hooked that up.
- 这么说她还能连累你 对吗 - 没错
- So she can still hurt you, right? - Yeah.
我要说的是任何能连累到你的人 都可能被警察利用
The point is anybody who can hurt you can be put into play.
- 我听到的越少越好 - 好的
- The less I hear, the better. - All right, yo.
嘿 把门带上好吗
Hey, yo, lock that door?
嘿 把门带上
Hey, yo, lock that door.
下面说说Bird和Bey
So we got Bird and Bey.
Bird不会招的
Bird will stand tall.
他已经入狱了 而Bey也快了
He already in jail, and Bey about to go, too.
Wee-Bey可硬着呢
And Wee-Bey hard like a rock.
接下来就是Savino
And we got Savino.
Savino清楚自己面临的不过是个小控罪
Savino know it ain't nothing but an Arm and Hammer charge.
我是说 他不会被它妈的 蹲三年牢房给吓傻的
I mean, he ain't gonna flip out over a motherfucking three years.
那倒是
True.
再下来就是除掉Orlando那破事
Then we got that shit with Orlando,
Little Man是唯一的麻烦
And the only problem there was Little Man.
曾经是
Was.
还有谁
Who else?
结束了 你的监听线失灵了
It's over, your wire's cold.
法院命令给了我们90天来监听5部电话
The court orders give me a total of 90 days on five phones.
我要监听满90天
I'm doing the full 90.
你想干坐着监听那几部
You want to sit listening to a bunch
破烂电话 这个没问题
Of broke-ass pay phones, have at it.
但干这事不需要那么多人力
But you don't need all that manpower to do it.
你想要些人回去 没问题 我能放走几个
You want some bodies back, I'll send a couple, no problem.
等一下 警督
Hold on, Lieutenant.
人是我给你的 该由我来决定谁回来
I gave you those people. I decide who comes back.
不过你不妨畅所欲言
But feel free to speak your mind,
你希望谁走谁留
If it were up to you.
他在问你话呢 警督
He asked you a question, Lieutenant.
我无所谓 你随意选吧
I have no opinion. Take your pick.
质押科那个老头叫啥名字来着
What's the name of that old detective from Pawnshop?
还有那个年轻人 Valchek脑残的女婿
And that young one, Valchek's brain-dead son-in-law.
Freamon Pryzbylewski
Freamon, Pryzbylewski.
留着他们吧
Keep them.
把Sydnor和Santangelo放回原部门
Send back Sydnor and Santangelo.
还有 警督
And, Lieutenant,
除了监听那些破电话...
If you want to do anything beyond...
你还想搞任何别的行动...
Listen to those dead phones...
得先向我报告
You need to brief me first.
干得不错 Cedric
You did good, Cedric.
你行动正确的话
You play your cards right,
你过去几个月来的工作...
All the work you did over the past few months...
会对你很有帮助
Will speak volumes for you.
还有Spurgeon警长说他将于11月底退休
And Maj. Spurgeon is saying that he's retiring at the end of November.
这就是说西北区虚位以待了
Which opens up the Northwest Command.
没错
That's right.
嗨 Ronnie 进来吧 请坐
Hi, Ronnie. Come in. Sit.
- Sheila 让Patrick进来 - 好的 先生
- Sheila, send Patrick in. - Yes, sir.
- 近来如何 - 我吗
- Anything up? - With me?
一样的破事 不同的案子
Same shit, different file.
- Barksdale案有什么情况 - 你收到我的报告了吗
- How about the Barksdale thing? - You've got my office reports?
监听线断了 我们正打算从他们的夜总会入手
Wire's dead, but we're looking into a bug in the man's nightclub.
除此之外呢 你们还做了什么
Aside from that, you're doing what?
调查Baltimore
Pulling campaign finance reports
每一位政客的竞选财务报告 对吗
For every politician in the city of Baltimore, right?
我吗
I am?
我们有吗
We are?
还有打电话给捐款人...
And making calls to some contributors...
问问题 做背景调查
Asking questions, doing background checks.
这事我全不知情
I don't know anything about this.
我说 Ronnie 你们它妈的想把这事搞多大
I mean, Ronnie, where the fuck is all this going?
那些报告都是公开的 不是吗 我是说...
Those are public reports, right? I mean....
他们要查也不用找我要传票啊
No one on that detail has come to me for any kind of subpoena.
你也被瞒住了?
You got back-doored, too?
为避免引起不必要的误会...
Just so there's no misunderstanding...
我决定把这个给你
I want to give you this.
我连任竞选委员会账户的支票复印件...
Copies of checks on the account of my re-election committee...
表明我返还了五笔捐款...
Representing the return of five separate contributions...
总共4500美元
Totaling $4,500.
还有这些...
Also copies of the checks...
捐赠人的支票复印件
From the donor are represented in there, too.
为维护统治 凯撒和被人怀疑的妻子离婚
如同凯撒的老婆该检点一点
Kind of like Caesar's wife and all that shit.
我能坦白的 也就这么五张支票了
The only thing that we could come up with were those five checks.
我不认识他们 也不知道他们为什么捐钱
And I don't know those people, and I don't know why they gave.
这些钱会立刻返还给捐赠人
That money's gonna be returned to the donors immediately.
各位 听我说
Guys, listen to me.
我它妈的一点也不知道
I don't know a fucking thing about
他们调查竞选捐款的事
Anyone looking at campaign contributions.
无论如何...
Be that as it may...
这些该足够证明我们清白了
This should make it clear that our hands are clean.
Ronnie 无论是谁在查这些 我要你带话给他们...
Ronnie, I want you to take that back to whoever's on the hunt...
我想让你告诉他们 以后别来烦我了
And I want you to tell them they've got no quarrel with me.
- 什么事 String - 哥们
- What's up, String? - dude.
你们想见我?
So y'all want to get with me?
对 我们要找你的一个小弟...
Yeah, we need to holler at your boy...
你知道 那个发现Omar姘头的小鬼
You know, the one that dimed on Omar's bitch.
我忘了他名字了
Can't recall his name.
哪一个
Which one?
那晚在Greek店那个
The one that was at the Greek's that night.
他通风报信 我们奖励了他
And we paid him for the lookout.
你们找他做什么
What y'all need him for?
关你什么事
What's it to you?
- 你们不用担心他了 - 你说什么
- You ain't got to worry about him. - Say what?
他走了 他不玩了
He's gone, he's out the game.
不玩了?
Out the game?
嘿 他问的是一个简单的问题
Yo, the man asked you a simple question.
我不想对你们不敬
I don't mean y'all no disrespect.
你们很清楚
You know I don't.
我只是告诉你们 那孩子不玩了
I am sitting here telling you that the boy is out the game.
况且即使他没有洗手不干
And even if he wasn't out the game,
他也不会成为你们的问题
He wouldn't be no problem.
但你知道 我们只是想跟他聊聊 Dee
But you know we just want to talk to him, Dee.
Avon
Avon...
放过他
Let the boy be.
放过他吧
Just let him be.
亲爱的 别老去动那该死的东西
Honey, just leave the damn thing alone.
你从哪弄来的 伙计
Where'd you get these, man?
Prevas
Prevas.
Broadway市集?
Broadway market?
城里最好的辣热狗
Best chili dogs in the city.
不 伙计 还不算
No, man, not even.
我赌十块你说不出更好的热狗了
I'll give you $10 if you can name a better dog.
Light大街George午餐店
George's Lunch on Light Street.
Greek连锁店?
The Greek joint?
你还在吸你妈的奶头时 那地方就已经停业了
That place closed back when you were still sucking on your mama's nipples.
我妈的奶头? 我昨晚还吸过她的奶头呢
My mama's nipples? I was sucking on them plums last night.
你欠我十块
You owe me $10.
我赌的是 举一个你吃得到的美味热狗的地方
I said, name a better dog you can have today,
不是历史上的
not in world history.
- 你只说了更好的热狗 - 你现在去给我买来看看
- You just said a better dog. - You go get that dog right now.
- 你买不来 - 而你只说举出更好的热狗
- You cannot go get that dog right now. - And you tell me the best fucking dog.
要吃得到的...
Physically--
你们就不能安静点吗 该死的我啥都听不到了
Can you please keep it down? I can't hear a goddamn thing!
如果你了解我的话就知道我赚的不多
You'd know how much I got if you laid something on me.
- 你喜欢那粉吗 - 只要你有
- You like that freeze? - If you holding.
会有的 要不我来这干嘛 明白吗
I'm fixing to be. That's why I'm here, you know?
我来这就是谈事情的
To discuss some things.
谈完之后 你再来找我
When you done discussing, you come back.
那好吧
All right, then.
保持这个姿势等着我 小妞
Hold that pose right there, shorty.
我会给你些好东西的
I'm gonna hook you up with some uncut.
你们这些小子话太多了
Y'all niggers talk too damn much, man.
她到底是什么人
Who the fuck is she?
治安队 专门维护公房治安
治安队的吗
Housing police?
不 她只是个普通市民 干保安的
No, she's one of them civilians they got doing security.
治安队穿的是灰制服
Housing cops wear the gray uniforms.
这么说她没配枪?
So she's not armed or nothing.
你觉得呢
Do she look it?
这么早就走?
You leaving early?
我来得早 我中午当班
I was early, I worked the lunch crowd.
她出来了
She's out.
有什么消息
Anything?
鸡毛蒜皮的闲扯
Table scraps.
我们想知道的是他们办公室里的谈话
What we want is being said in that office.
没什么借口让Shardene待在里面 获取我们想要的信息
There's no reason for Shardene to be in there long enough for us to get it.
拆了吧 我做不下去了
Take it out, I can't do this anymore.
你不用勉强 亲爱的
You won't have to, darling.
我总觉得他们会看出来 我要退出
I think they'll look at me and know. I need to quit.
我们不会强迫你戴窃听器 好吗 亲爱的
I don't need you wearing this wire, all right, honey?
你只用再进去帮我们办一件事
I just need you to go in there and do one more thing.
看看那个乡下仔
Look at this country nigger.
- 该死 Wallace - Wally
- Damn, Wallace. - Wally!
他不停哭闹着让我寄钱给他搭巴士
He kept crying till I sent him bus money.
好啦 我只是厌倦了一成不变的乡村生活
All right. I just got tired of that same old country scenery.
对我来说 日子过得太慢了
It was just too slow for me.
是啊 不过你有没有找两个村姑?
Yeah, but did you get some of that country ass?
就算有 也是四条腿的
And if he did, it was on four legs.
哥们 他们那没有农场
Nigger, they got no farms down there, man,
不过倒是有些土包子
But they did have some Bamas though.
周六晚上跑Sears商场玩
They got their Saturday night shit down at Sears.
- 他们就像 你知道 - 眼泪 对吗 你都快哭了
- They was like, you know-- - Tears, right? You were about to cry.
你就在那买的虎胆龙威鞋?
That where you got them Die-Hards?
大哥 这是Timbs牌
Man, these Timbs.
没错 是Timbs的 看得出它们边上的树
Yeah, they Timbs. I can see the tree on the side of them.
那么 你能让我回来管钱吗
So you gonna put me back on the money?
慢着
Hold.
听着 就算我们让你回来...
Look, if we do put you back on...
你也得从望风干起 伙计
You have to start as lookout, man.
你出城度假的时候就没你位子了 小子
You lost your spot when you bucked town, dawg.
拜托 真男人会跟兄弟们待在一起...
Come on, a real man would stay with his people...
他不会一见血就跑路
He wouldn't run at the first sight of some blood.
怎么报警还是会的吧?
Y'all can still holler 5-0, right?
如果他想回来管钱 那就这样吧
If he want back on the money, he back on the money.
如果他想的话
If he want it.
我们的小伙可能还想着 回Edmondson中学...
My man might be thinking of going back to Edmondson...
就像我们之前聊的那样 对吧
Iike we talked about, right?
来吧 小子 散个步
Come on, nigger, let's walk.
哥们 你不会真的上了啥动物吧 有吗
Dawg, you ain't cornholed no animal for real, did you?
- 再说啊 Poot - 你个傻帽
- Go ahead, Poot. - You're stupid.
Sean John：嘻哈风格的衣服品牌
别弄坏了我的Sean John
Don't be fucking with my Sean John.
这案子归谁
So who caught it?
Garvey
Garvey.
他知道死者曾做过证人...
He knows about the whole witness angle...
但在事情搞清楚前 他还不想上报
But he doesn't want to run it up to the bosses until he knows more.
为什么现在要除掉Nakeisha Lyles
Why ace Nakeisha Lyles now?
因为他们知道我们来真的了
Because now they know we're for real.
Avon在忙着擦屁股
Avon's cleaning house all the way.
先是那些电话没用了 然后是
First the phones go dead and then anyone
他认为我们会加以利用的人
He thinks we might be able to flip.
那孩子怎样了
What about the boy?
我操
Fuck me.
我们周五把他送去海边
We took him to the shore Friday
原计划是周一把他带回来见大陪审团
And the plan was to bring him back up on the Monday for the grand jury.
- 然后呢 - Greggs中枪了
- And what happened? - Greggs got shot.
是Reese州警吗
Trooper Reese?
我是Baltimore警局的Daniels警督
This is Lieutenant Daniels with the Baltimore Department.
有没有谁离Cambridge比较近...
Is there someone that can go near Cambridge...
能去看看我们藏在那的一个小孩
Check on a kid we got stashed down there?
- 打给他 - 不 那边没电话
- Call him. - No, there's no phone there.
- 请等一下 - 我等着 好的
- Can you hang on? - I'll hold, yeah.
让Sydnor从车辆调配场调车
Have Sydnor pull a car from motor pool.
我们今晚把那孩子接回来睡沙发...
We get the kid back up here tonight, he sleeps on my sofa...
明天送他去见大陪审团
And we grand-jury him in the morning.
- 你那脱衣舞娘怎样 - 她很勇敢
- What about your stripper? - The woman's got heart.
我的意思是 我想把她保护起来
I mean, I want her protected.
不能再死人了 听见了吗
No more bodies, hear?
我那儿有地方 她可以跟我住
I got room at my place, she can lay up with me.
这个我无所谓
I got no problem with that.
别忘了你的本分
Remember who you are, Detective.
保护民众 服务民众 队长 保护民众 服务民众
Protect and serve, Lieutenant. Protect and serve.
我想告诉你 这的事
I'm saying, this here game,
已经与你无关了 伙计
It ain't gonna work for you no more, man.
你的离开造成了一些麻烦
You leaving, you stirred up some shit.
- 我是说 这不是你的错 - Dee 听着
- I'm saying it ain't your fault. - Dee, look.
我很感激你为我做的和对我说的一切
I appreciate what you trying to say and all,
但我生于斯长于斯 好吗
But I grew up in the courts, all right?
我和这帮家伙一路走来
I been with them niggers since forever.
这就是我的家 懂吗
This is home, right?
你没听懂我的话 Wallace 你没听懂我的话
You ain't hearing me, Wallace. You ain't hearing me,
无论谁问你你还干不干了
Anybody asks you whether you in this game..
你都要告诉他这是你毕生事业 行吗
You tell them you in it for life, all right?
你会努力工作 小心办事...
You play it hard, you play it tight...
确保那些家伙相信你永远是他们一边的
And make sure niggers know you gonna stand by your people.
别说漏了嘴 别有二心 也别告密
No loose talk, no second thoughts, and no snitching.
就这么干
Play it like that.
你来这干嘛 迷路了吗
What you doing down in the PJ's, you lost?
我在找你
I'm looking for you.
你知道我在这做正事
You know I be down here working.
做正事也得吃饭啊
A working man got to eat.
- 我最爱的香鱼蛋糕? - 撒盐饼干上加了芥末
- My favorite spicy fish cakes? - On the saltines with the mustard.
我感动得都要哭了
You gonna make me cry, you know.
我要走了 要回去工作
I need to get up out of here and get back to it.
- 注意安全 好了 - 你也是
- You be safe. All right. - You, too.
这东西
This here.
Sterling餐厅的 小子 我们可以大快朵颐了
Sterling's, baby, we're about to feast.
Sterling餐厅什么玩意
What the hell is Sterling's?
Sterling餐厅 29街那个 你不知道吗
Sterling's, up on 29th Street? Don't you know nothing?
操 如果不是在西区 我知道才怪
Shit, if it ain't up on the Westside, I don't know shit.
因为这儿...
'Cause this shit...
这儿才是我的地盘
This is me, yo, right here.
她是谁 你的新马子什么的吗?
Who was that, your new girl or something?
不 小子 她是我妈
No, nigger, that's my mom.
认识Davis参议员吗
You know Senator Davis?
不 长官
No, sir.
警督
Lieutenant.
Clay想见你
Clay wanted to meet you,
看看他有什么能帮你
See if there was any help he can offer.
帮我?
Help?
显然 你的人在调查财务报告...
Your people are apparently pulling finance reports...
以及查证一些捐款人
And checking up on some of the contributors.
我想当面向你保证
I wanted to reassure you on that front.
我跟毒品案无关 警督
I'm not involved in drugs, Lieutenant.
很好
Good.
还有件牵涉到参议员司机的事
And this business with the senator's driver.
Price先生 名Damien
Mr. Price, Damien.
Day-Day
Day-Day.
Price那件事
This business with Mr. Price,
完全是个误会...
This is a misunderstanding...
没有必要惊动警察
That is really of no concern to the police.
他怀揣2万美元现金...
He had $20,000 of cash on him...
而这笔钱是公房区大楼 一个贩毒嫌疑人给他的
Delivered out of a project tower by a known drug suspect.
这笔钱被按面额整理 包装好
The money was banded and manicured by denomination.
这其中并没有涉及犯罪
There's no crime here.
那些钱Damien早带在身上了...
That was money that Damien already had on him...
早在他去Franklin大楼前
When he drove down to Franklin Terrace.
那些钱来自前一周末的募款活动
Money from a cash-bar fundraiser the previous weekend.
我们有一份修订财务报告可以证明
We filed an amended finance report that shows--
好吧
Fine.
没有搜查Price先生的理由
There's no probable cause for a search of Mr. Price.
我想这点我们一致同意
I think we are in agreement on that.
不 我们有理由进行搜查
No, there was PC for the search.
你是说你有证据
You're saying you have evidence
表明一名参议员侍从涉嫌毒品案?
That a senatorial aide is involved in drugs?
我是说我们有理由截下Price
I'm saying we had reason to stop Mr. Price
并对他搜身 并在搜查后发现
And effect a body search, after which we discovered
包装好的2万美元现金
$20,000 in cash in banded, manicured bills.
这就是我要说的
That's all I'm saying.
你能向这个混球解释一下 他妈的他到底在做什么吗
Will you explain to this motherfucker just what it is he's doing here?
- Daniels警督 - 抱歉 长官
- Lt. Daniels-- - Excuse me, sir.
事情很简单
But it's pretty basic.
如果参议员没有涉及任何违法行为...
If the senator is not involved in anything illegal...
那他完全不必担心
Then he doesn't need to worry.
我说的再清楚不过了
I can't be any clearer about it than that.
笨蛋 你他妈怎么想的
Fool, what do you think?
你以为我们知道谁给的钱?
That we know anything about who gives money?
我们会它妈的在意 他们是谁或他们想要什么?
That we give a damn about who they are or what they want?
我们才不会查他们或他们的过去
We have no way of running down them or their stories.
我们不在乎
We don't care.
我们不过兑现支票 唱票 然后继续前进
We just cash the damn checks, count the votes, and move on.
还有什么要说得吗 Burrell副局长?
Anything else, Deputy Burrell?
各位 失陪
Gentlemen.
你该把他踢到步行送信的穷乡僻壤去...
You need to put his ass on a foot post so far out in the sticks...
远到让他可以看见费城的警察向他走来(两地接壤)
That he's gonna see the Philadelphia cops walking towards him.
你现在别跟我说了 Erv
Now you just ain't talking to me now, Erv.
你去跟市长说...
You talking to the Mayor...
跟市委员会说 跟州中央委员会说
The city caucus, the state central committee.
现在 你们是在太岁头上动土
And right now, you got your hand in our pocket.
第十八 亲爱的
Eighteen, baby!
高高在上的十八名 亲爱的
Eighteen with a bullet, baby.
警司(级别高于警探)Hauk报到 长官
Det. Sgt. Hauk reporting for duty, sir.
更好玩的是 Carver是37名
And the best part? Carver's 37.
你知道 记住手下警号有好处
You know, it helps if you know them by the numbers.
会让你听上去得更专业
It makes you sound more professional.
它妈的Carver在职培训回来后
Fucking Carver he gets back from in-service training,
就得亲我的杠子了 我要让他亲我的杠子
He's gonna kiss the stripes. I'm gonna make him kiss the stripes.
- 恭喜 - 谢谢 长官 非常感激
- Congratulations. - Thank you, sir. Appreciate it.
Hauk警司?
Sgt. Hauk?
老天爷 帮帮忙
God help us.
- Daniels - Daniels 我是州警Reese
- Daniels. - Daniels, this is Trooper Reese.
孩子的祖母说他已经走了两天了
Grandmother says this kid's been gone two days.
Wallace离开那了 已经两天了
Wallace is out of pocket. Two days.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - Yeah.
高层区也没新货?
Ain't no re-up in the towers, neither?
- 停业喽 - 好吧
- Shop dead, yo. - all right.
- 怎么样 伙计 - 老样子
- What up, man? - Same old.
那小子怎样了
What's up with that boy?
他就一废物 如此而已
He's just a punk, that's all.
Dee让他继续管钱
Dee put him back on count though.
哦? 我听说他洗手不干了
Word? I heard he was out the game.
是的 不过现在又回来了
He was, but he back now.
他之前去哪儿了
Where he been at?
他说去乡下奶奶家了
Down his granny house, he says.
嗯 他奶奶家
Right, his granny house.
听说他吓得差点尿裤子...
I heard he damn near shit his pants...
当他看到Omar的姘头的下场的时候
When he saw what happened to Omar's bitch.
他只是天生不是这块料
He just ain't built for this, you know.
他心脏泵的都是儿童饮料
His heart pump Kool-Aid.
嗯 那么你呢
Right. What about you?
你天生是这块料?
You built for this shit?
毫无疑问
No doubt.
做好干活的准备了吗
You ready to put the work in?
有家伙吗
You got heat?
很好 士兵
All right, soldier.
楼上没人
It's clear upstairs.
没有外接电线(之前房子有偷电) 没有果汁盒
No extension cords. No juice boxes.
没有Wallace
No Wallace.
该死 哥们 Chink Bob餐厅...
Dang, boy, Chink Bob's...
从不在包装袋里放餐巾纸
Never be putting no napkins in the bag.
混蛋 餐巾纸又贵又废
Motherfucker, because napkins expensive and shit.
我的钱也是
So is my money.
好吧 来 过来 来吃点东西
All right, come on, go. Something to eat?
你们都知道这有什么
Y'all know what's here.
动起来 你们都过来吃中国菜...
Let's go, y'all need to get up in this Chinese food...
因为 你们也知道 我现在手头紧啊
'cause, you know, I'm looking kind of needy right about now.
在听什么呢 慢点 先把盘子拿出来
What you listening to? Hold up, take them plates first.
Big Tymers(嘻哈组合)106th&Park在播他们的新歌
Big Tymers, their new video on 106th and Park.
- 106th&Park? - " The joint is vicious"(大麻有毒) - "有毒"?
- 106th and Park? is vicious? - The joint is vicious.
- 嗯 - 真的吗 他们怎么称呼你的 小家伙
- Yeah. - For real? What they call you?
- Buff(健美骑士) 因为我有身材 - 你有身材?
- Buff, 'cause I got the stuff. yeah. - You got the stuff?
Buff 你要吃一点蛋卷什么的
Buff, you need to get up in these egg rolls or something.
有那孩子的消息吗
Any word on the kid?
我拿着他的照片在Cambridge 找了一晚上
I rolled around Cambridge all night with his B of l.
如果他还在那 没人见过他
If he's down there, he ain't got no profile.
我们让西部和中部的警车帮忙寻找
We got lookouts to every car in the Western and Central.
还正准备试试找他母亲
We're trying for an address on his mother.
探员
Detective.
队长
Lieutenant.
监听线断了...
Wire's dead...
上面命令我们把人放回原部门
So we've been ordered to begin sending bodies home.
Sydnor会再待一段时间 因为Cantrell欠我的
Sydnor, we have a little longer, because Cantrell still owes me.
你跟Rawls没问题吧
You okay with Rawls?
我满足了他结案的要求 不是吗
I gave him his clearance, right?
他还能拿我怎样
What's he gonna do to me?
继续保持吧 Sanny
Keep it warm, Sanny.
那是什么
What's that?
Orlando俱乐部上层的设计图
Plans for what is now Orlando's. The upper floors.
这是隔壁大楼的设计图
This is the property next door.
- 你怎么这么快就弄到了 - CoStar(美国房地产市场分析公司)那儿查的
- How'd you get them so quick? - CoStar search.
我们计划在办公室装个远程麦克风
Plan is to get a remote mike into the office.
可能的话甚至可以装光纤摄像头
Maybe even some fiber-optics.
只是我们现在还不知道Avon办公室在哪
Only we don't know where Avon's office is yet.
这就是Shardene能提供大帮助的地方了
Which is where Shardene helps us out in a big way.
她要怎么做
What she gonna do?
拿出一个卷尺 让Avon拿着另一端?
Take out a tape and ask Avon to hold the other end?
难道你们都没在军队里待过吗
Ain't none of y'all ever been in the military?
知道怎么即时测量30英寸吗
How do you learn a 30-inch, quick-time?
逃避兵役 享受和平的怪胎们
Draft-dodging peace-freaks.
- 给我拿把尺和一些线来 - 为什么我去
- Get me a ruler and some string. - Why me?
为啥
Why?
因为那人这么说 就这原因
Because the man said so, that's why.
- Wallace不会告密的 - 伙计 你怎么知道
- Wallace ain't no snitch. - Man, how you know?
你能知道他之前究竟去了哪吗
How you know where he been running to?
他吸了毒 我看见他拿的
He was getting high. I've seen him cop.
他大概只是跑去海边把毒戒掉
He probably went down to the shore to clean that shit up.
伙计 果真如此 那他就不可靠了
Man, if he using, then you know he ain't reliable.
拜托 想想
Come on, think.
听着 那人给了我们指令 懂吗
Look, the man gave the word, all right?
我们要么执行 要么滚蛋
We either step up or we step the fuck off.
游戏就是这样玩的
That's the game.
这就是它妈的游戏规则
That's the fucking game.
Cedric
Cedric.
你有没有听说Baltimore的
You ever hear of an elected official
一个竞选办公室把钱退还给捐款人?
In Baltimore giving money back?
不管你们在干什么 你们把我上司吓出屎来了
Whatever you're doing scared my boss shitless.
他叫我去他办公司 然后给了我这个
He calls me in and hands me that.
请原谅我对我们的调查刨根问底
Forgive me for prying into the details of our investigation.
我知道 这很烦人
I know, it's annoying.
但你们这帮子到底在干什么
But what the hell are you guys doing?
嗯?
Yeah?
这些是Avon的钱吗
Is that Avon's money?
东区的地址...
Eastside addresses...
不过也许Barksdale还有我们未知的幌子
But maybe Barksdale has fronts we don't know about.
州检察长退还的款项?
State's attorney's returning this?
尽快退还的
Fast as he can.
你们在这搞出一堆破事
Y'all are stirring some shit here.
为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
不告诉你 对你来说不是更理想吗
Aren't you better off that we didn't?
记得我妈以前带我来过
I remember my mom used to bring me here.
还去过一个叫Fruit Fantasy的餐厅
We used to go to a place called Fruit Fantasy.
比如橙汁苏打之类的?
Like orange soda, some shit like that?
不 都是新鲜的
No, these shits was fresh.
虽然我妈总把巴卡第鸡尾酒掺进去
My mom used to pour mad Bacardi in hers though.
肯定掺了不少吧
Wasn't much she didn't pour it into.
你看看你 像个孩子似地把妈妈挂嘴边
Look at you, talking about your mama like you're still a kid.
我当然会想到她
I got to thinking on her.
你们它妈的也不可能总那么坚强吧
Your ass ain't got to be hard all the goddamn time, neither.
脆弱的一环会毁掉整条锁链
Soft link break the chain.
你到底是 男孩还是男人?
What are you, a boy or a man?
我是个男人
I'm a man.
我们接下来做什么 男人们 去找点乐子?
So what are we gonna do, man, go have some fun?
好了 是这一层
Okay, on this floor.
倒数第二间房
It's the second room from the rear.
房前30步是楼梯...
The stairs start 30 paces from the front...
有24阶 每级约一英尺
There's 24 stairs, about a foot each.
当你来到顶楼后...
When you get to the top floor...
走8步到更衣室门口...
It's eight paces to the door of the dressing room...
再走10步是个密室
And then another 10 to the back room.
前门算起80到110步间
80 to 1 10 in from the front.
这栋建筑三楼是空的
Third floor of this building is vacant.
否则我们就得要授权书了
Otherwise we'd need a warrant.
- 15块 - 这是10块 拿着
- $15. - Here take $10.
- 15块 - 混球 我没见计价器
- $15. - Motherfucker, I don't see no meter.
它妈的滚蛋
Get the fuck out of here.
现在是凌晨2:30
It's 2:30 in the morning.
慢慢来 手指粗的孔就差不多了
Easy now. Hole only needs to be as big as your finger.
不过不是你那种香肠指
Not those Esskay sausage-looking fingers you got.
你知道啥叫巨掌
You know what big hands mean.
你知道啥叫巨掌 是吧
You know what big hands mean, right?
队长...
Lieutenant...
我刚查到Wallace母亲的新住址
I just pulled a fresh address for Wallace's mother.
这里交给我们吧
We're okay here.
你们都藏哪儿了
Where y'all at?
好吧 要让我找到你们 就有你们好看的
All right, when I find y'all, y'all gonna get it.
还是现在出来的好
You better come out now.
你们在哪啊
Where y'all at?
听着 现在可不是陪你们捉迷藏的时候
Look, I'm not even playing with y'all right about now.
听见了没
You hear me?
游戏结束 你们它妈的到底在哪
Game over. Where the fuck y'all at?
要让我找到你们 我可要打屁屁了
When I find y'all, I'm beating your asses.
现在你们到底在哪
Now where y'all at?
可别让我找到你们
Don't let me find y'all.
Poot 看这个 Little Man把他的播放器落在这了
Check this, Poot. Little Man left his player and shit.
你是个软蛋 伙计
You a weak-ass nigger, man.
你就应该待着乡下不要回来 哥们
You should've stayed down in the country, man.
你们都是我兄弟啊
Y'all my niggers, yo.
你它妈的自找的 伙计
You fucking brought this on yourself.
- 我们亲如兄弟 - 你自找的
- We boys! - You brought this on yourself.
为什么要搞成这样
Why it gotta be like this?
我们上辈子就是兄弟了 记得吗
You my niggers from B.C., remember that?
拜托 你它妈的还尿裤子
Come on, wetting your fucking pants,
跟个小鬼一样 做个男子汉
Like you a little boy. Be a man!
像个他妈的男子汉一样站好
Stand up like a motherfucking man.
- 你们都是我兄弟啊 - 你自己说你是个男子汉的 站直了
- Y'all my niggers. - You said you a fucking man. Stand up straight!
我们是兄弟啊
That's us, man.
开枪啊 该死 要做就...
Do it goddamnit, if you....
Darcia Wallace? 我们是来找你儿子的
Darcia Wallace? We're looking for your son.
我们想你可能知道他的下落
Thought you might help us out as to his whereabouts.
谁的下落
Where-a-who?
靠 我也一直在找那个混小子
Shit, I be looking for that smart little nigger, too.
- 那小子从我这拿了10块钱 - 最近吗
- Boy took me for $10. - Recently?
- 发生什么事了 - 没事
- What's going on out there? - Nothing.
两个警察在我想喝酒时来打断我
Couple of police interrupting me, while I'm trying to get my drink on.
你儿子可能有危险
Your son might be in some danger.
他要敢回来 危险也不小
He gonna be in some danger right here if he shows up.
问也不问就从我包里拿了10块钱
Snatched that $10 out my purse without asking.
我要把他眼珠子扇出来
I'll slap the bright out his eyes.
这是我名片
Here's my card.
你碰上他了 给我打电话
You run into him, you call me.
- 你们开吉普来的? - 就在外面 伙计
- Y'all got ajeep? - Over there, man.
好 来看看我们有什么要做的
All right, let's see what we got here.
他在打包
He's packing shit up.
你在那抓耳挠腮的干嘛 伙计
What you scratching your head for, man?
你怎么把这保险箱弄进来的 怎么就弄不出去了?
How y'all get the safe in here, and you can't get it out?
打911 谁接电话就跟谁说
Just dial 911 and talk to whoever pick up.
别报名字之类的
Don't say your name or nothing.
他们房门上有个动物救助热线的广告
就说屋子里有只受伤的小动物...
Just say there's been an animal hurt inside the house...
然后 你就挂断
And then you hang up.
怎么了 有什么事要我干的
What up? So what do you need from me?
我要你去趟纽约帮我取点东西
I need you to run up to N. Y.C. to pick up a little something.
听着 我知道我们被搞惨了
Look, I know we tapped and all.
靠 每个人都等着新货
Shit, everybody waiting on the re-up,
但我从来没跑过啊
But I never made that run before.
听着 我觉得我的身边没有几个
Listen, I feel like I don't have that many people around me
值得信赖的人
I could really trust.
血浓于水啊 你理解吗
Not like I can kin. You follow me?
- 好吗 - 有多少
- All right? - How much is it?
只需要维持周转
We just need to maintain.
足够维持高层区的市场就行
Put out enough so we can keep hold of them towers.
何时出发
When?
今晚
Tonight.
好吧
All right.
我开什么去
What am I driving?
- 租车 不要太显眼的 - 去哪租
- A rental, no flash. - Where from?
我不知道去哪租 伙计 机场附近随便一个租车点
I don't know where from, man, one of those places by the airport.
- 喂 - 我们有料了
- Yeah. - We got something real.
- 我这就过来 - 好的
- I'm on my way. - All right.
该死
Shit!
哪一辆
Which one?
那边那辆租的福特金牛
The rental there, the Taurus.
不得不说 队长 你从联邦探员那弄来了好东西啊
I gotta say, Lieutenant, you got mad suction with the federales.
喂 我是Daniels
Yeah, Daniels.
好的
Yeah.
在哪
Where?
Wallace?
...戒毒所工程 ...2.5亿美金  ...发展补助金
可怜的混小子
Poor fucking kid.
Wallace一死 Stringer就逃过一劫了
With Wallace gone, that's Stringer out of the box.
他居然是去里面换它妈的衣服
He was in there changing his fucking clothes.
你相信吗
You believe that?
小子得弄好门面
Boy had to get himself correct.
开始了
We're on.
不用盯梢 由卫星监视就行
No need for an eyeball. Let the satellite do the work.
不如我打给我律师...
How about I call my lawyer...
让他来跟你慢慢解释好吗
Have him explain that whole profiling thing to you?
Barksdale先生 我们的收费站摄像头...
Mr. Barksdale, our tollbooth cameras...
拍到你在23:10时通过G.W.大桥...
Have you on the G.W. Bridge at 2310 hours...
35分钟后又从同一出口进入收费公路
Then re-entering the turnpike at the same exit 35 minutes later.
为什么你大老远地跑到纽约去就待半小时
Why did you drive all the way to New York for half an hour?
从车里出来 先生
Step out of the car, sir.
手放在我看得见的地方
Keep your hands where I can see them.
转身 面朝汽车 手放在车顶
Turn around, face the car, put your hands on the roof.
- 你是否携有武器 先生 - 没有
- Are you carrying any weapons, sir? - No.
- 刀具 尖利物? - 没有
- Any knives, any needles? - No.
有没有什么我需要知道的非法持有物
Any illegal substances I should know about?
好了 双腿分开
Okay. Spread your legs back.
双腿再分开点
Spread your legs back more.
好 慢慢把你右手放到背后
Okay, slowly bring your right arm around your back.
现在 另一只手
Now bring the other one.
- 记得我吗 - 我要律师
- Remember me? - Lawyer.
放松 我们才刚开始
Easy. We're just getting started.
我要律师 混球
Lawyer, motherfucker.
好吧 你很强硬
Okay, so you're hard,
但你猜怎么着 我才不在乎
But guess what? I could give a fuck.
你? 我已经厌倦了你的小花招
You? I'm tired of your games.
怎么 你想让我写封信或者别的什么?
What, you want me to write a letter, or some shit like that?
我们不需要耍花招
No game we need to run.
你因携带一公斤毒品被捕
You're popped with a kilo of uncut.
这事不怪你 你一路小心谨慎
Not that you messed up. You did everything right.
限速 打转向灯 开尾灯
Speed limit, turn signals, working taillights.
你该问的是...
Question you gotta ask is...
那些州警是怎么想到把你拦下的?
How'd those troopers know to pull you over?
搞砸的另有其人 明白吗
Someone else fucked up. You following me?
但他们只会归罪于你 要坐牢的也是你
But it's you they're gonna blame, and you who's gonna do the jolt.
律师
Lawyer.
是要找Levy 对吗
That'd be Levy, right?
他从你舅舅那儿拿酬劳 不是吗
He's getting paid by your uncle, is that right?
是啊 他为你们擦屁股
Yeah, he's looking out for your interests.
比你好
More than you.
听着...
Listen...
我不会再说任何事...
I ain't saying another damn thing...
给任何人听 除了我的律师
To nobody but my lawyer.
顺便说一句...
By the way...
你小弟Wallace 在低层区被枪杀了
Your boy Wallace, shot dead in the low-rises.
这就是你们所谓的照顾自己人 是吗
That's how y'all take care of your own, right?
你是个谎话连篇的混球
You're a lying motherfucker.
那又怎样
So what?
你是要我也写封信给他老妈吗
You want me to write a letter to his mom, too?
它妈的滚出去
Get the fuck out of here.
你不应该这样把他派出去
You didn't have to send him the way you did.
自己开车?
In one car?
他该再带上些人
He should've been trailing a mule.
95号公路还是火车根本没区别...
95 or on the train, it don't make no difference...
他压根就不该一个人去
He shouldn't have been there alone.
- 你看 Brianna - 难道你不知道有"改装车"(毒贩改装的运货车)吗
- Look here, Brianna-- - Ain't you ever heard of a trap-car?
你让我儿子去纽约...
You send my son to New York...
开着一辆它妈的租用车...?
In a motherfucking rental...
还只是让他把货放在后车厢里?
And you just let him ride with that package in the trunk?
- 我很抱歉 - 抱歉不会让他免受牢狱之灾
- I'm sorry-- - That won't bring him out of prison!
好歹你得让那个犹太律师 做自己该做的事 成吗
Better make sure that Jew lawyer of yours earns his money, all right?
好的 不过D'Angelo也得有点担当
All right. D'Angelo gonna have to do his part.
你想说什么
Meaning what?
你喜欢你现在开的车 对吧
You like the car you driving there, right?
你喜欢这间小屋吗 我送你的 喜欢吧
You like this crib? I put you in this crib. You like it?
没错 我是说 我们都有很多东西要守护
Yeah, I mean, we all got a lot to protect here.
你得提醒他这点
You need to remind him of that.
好让他在事到临头时能挺起腰杆
So when it come down to it, he can stand up tall.
你不用担心我的孩子
You ain't gotta worry about my child.
我把他养大 教得好好的
I raised that boy, and I raised him right.
又不是我搞砸的
It wasn't me who fucked up.
真的吗 那谁搞砸的
Really? So who did?
我们它妈的又怎么会在这里?
Why the fuck are we here?
听着 你唯一要做的就是等着保释听证会
Listen, all you need to do is keep your head through the bail hearing.
我们很有机会让你回家
We got a good shot at bringing you home here.
然后呢
Then what?
谁来为那辆车后车厢那个麻烦买单
Who gonna take the weight for all the shit in the trunk of that car?
Wallace在哪
Where's Wallace at?
那小子在哪 String?
Where's the boy, String?
D'Angelo 闭嘴
D'Angelo, shut your mouth.
Wallace在哪 我就想知道这个
Where's Wallace? That's all I want to know.
小子 你最好三思
Kid, you better think.
它妈的Wallace在哪
Where the fuck is Wallace?
嗯? String
Huh? String!
String 看着我
String. Look at me!
看着我 它妈的Wallace在哪
Look at me! Where the fuck is Wallace?
我不想让这个衣冠禽兽替我打官司
I don't want this Payless-wearing motherfucker representing me.
我自己找人 好吧
I'm gonna get my own man, all right?
所以你滚回车上
So just get back in your car,
它妈的自己开回去吧
And get the fuck back down south.
好吧 你个愚蠢的狗娘养的
All right, you stupid motherfucker.
你爱怎样怎样
You made your decision.
是啊 我爱怎样怎样 Wallace在哪
Yeah, I made my decision. Where's Wallace at?
它妈的Wallace在哪
Where the fuck is Wallace?
Wallace在哪 String?
Where's Wallace, String?
String 它妈的Wallace在哪
String, where the fuck is Wallace?
Stringer
Stringer!
抓了他 你们完成任务了
Bring him in. You're done.
为什么
Why?
我们想的话随时可以起诉他
We have the charge whenever we want it.
为什么不等等看办公室的监视情况
Why not stay up on the bug we've got in his office?
那件事你可没向我报告
The bug you didn't brief me about.
我还以为你的小鸟每时每刻都会向你报告...
I thought your little bird told you everything we did...
我们的所有事情呢
A minute after we did it.
我们中有人因此受伤 这件案子总得有个结果
One of our people got hurt. That's supposed to mean something.
我们一直在追捕凶手...
We're hunting her shooters...
并且通过上帝的保佑和你们有力的工作
And by the grace of God and your good work...
我们已经能对主要目标立案
We've got a viable case on our main target.
就以试图从纽约
Just charge Barksdale
购买并运回毒品的罪名起诉Barksdale
With the attempt purchase from New York and bring it all home.
那Stringer呢 他们的二号人物?
What about Stringer, his number two?
那个证人小孩被杀 他就脱罪了
He slipped off the hook when we lost the boy witness.
我们尽力了
We've done all we can.
你听明白了吗
Are you hearing me?
这些是开枪打伤警察的责任人
These are the people responsible for dropping a police.
不只是凶手 还有那些幕后黑手
Not just the shooters, but the ones who make the dirt happen.
我要真正把他们清理干净 而不是给他们小小的打击
I'm trying to put them down for real, not for some short-time bit.
你想做的就这些?
That all you're trying to do?
如果你想做的就这些 为什么让你的人...
If that's all you're doing, how is it you have people...
查竞选记录和财务报告?
Pulling campaign records and finance reports?
查那些他妈的有什么屁用
What the fuck has that got to do with anything?
资金流向是我调查的一部分
The money is part of my case.
以前有一段时间 我可以容忍...
There was a time when I was willing to say otherwise...
你和你朋友保有一些黑暗的角落 但现在不行了
To let you and all your friends hide some of that dirt, but not now.
你想跟我谈黑暗? 那就谈吧
You want to talk about dirt? Have at it.
谈谈你在东区干的那些破事
Talk some shit about your Eastern district days.
谈谈过去到底发生了什么
Talk about what was going on back
当你管理缉毒组的时候吧
When you was running wild in the DEU.
那只是以讹传讹
That's just talk.
以讹传讹?
Just talk?
FBI调查报告
FBI field reports.
你挣了不少快钱啊
You came into a lot of money, quick.
你也会很快进监狱...
And you can go to jail just as quick...
如果我开始问一些正确的问题
If I start asking the right questions.
了结这案子 要不了结你自己
This case ends, or you are done.
该死 我甚至不需要你去抓Barksdale
Hell, I don't even need you to lock up Barksdale.
我会让你的警长知会你的探员们
I'll have your major debrief your detectives
让他们自己去弄逮捕令
And type the warrants himself.
这案子到此为止
This case is done!
你想怎样就怎样
You do what you feel.
你想查到一半就抓Avon? 请自便
You wanna pull Avon in on half a case? You go ahead.
你想把我的事公之于众? 请随意
You wanna put my shit in the street? Feel free.
不过东区有的是内幕 我的不过是一小部分
But the Eastern had a lot of stories. Mine ain't the only one.
很多人都从东区过来的
A lot of people came through that district.
如果你想整我 早就动手了
If you were gonna do me, I'd already be done.
但你最怕的就是报纸上 一个影响很坏的头条 不是吗
But there ain't nothing you fear more than a bad headline now, is there?
你宁愿生活在粪坑里 也不愿让人知道你挖粪
You'd rather live in shit than let the world see you work a shovel.
你可以签署逮捕令 我会照办
You can order warrants, and I'll serve them.
但只要我还管着这断掉的监听线...
But as long as I have days left on those dead wires...
这案子就要查下去
This case goes on.
嘿 看看这些自以为是 特种部队的傻帽 伙计
Yo, look at these Delta Force motherfuckers, man.
- 看看他们 - 好的
- Look at them. - All right.
Levy那边怎样
What's up with Levy?
他说会来见我们
He said he gonna meet us down there.
我还是没把这保险箱搬出去
I still didn't get this safe out of here yet, man.
- 里面有多少钱 - 十五万美金
- How much money in it? - $150,000.
十五万?
$150,000?
那就开着吧 伙计 没必要弄坏这么好一个保险箱
Open it up, man. No sense in ruining a good safe.
这个没有我想象的那么好玩
This isn't as much fun as I thought it would be.
这些特警队的家伙真喜欢 用他们那玩具破门而入啊 不是吗
The SWAT guys do love to break out their toys,don't they?
他们以为楼上是Tony Montana(《疤面煞星》角色)啊?
They think it's Tony Montana up there?
他们怕是多年没碰枪了
They probably haven't touched a gun in years.
去它妈的
Fuck this shit.
我们上吧 队长
You and me, Lieutenant.
巷里是哪个组?
What units are in the alley?
谁守着后门
Any sightline to the rear door?
收到 谁守着屋顶
10-4, who has the roof?
听我指挥冲进去
We're gonna move in on my command.
所有人待命
Everyone stand by.
我们今天不需要动用你们的人 叫他们退后
We're not gonna need your men today. Call them back.
- 等等 - 这是我的案子 叫你的人退下
- Now wait a minute-- - My case, back your men off.
改天再对付你
Catch you later.
本市戒毒所工程 收到2.5亿联邦发展补助金
不错
Good.
Barksdale带上手铐了
Barksdale's wearing bracelets.
还没找到Wee-Bey和Little Man?
Still no Wee-Bey, no Little Man?
没有 销声匿迹了
No, nothing there.
逮捕
这是我办过最棒的案子
This is the best work I ever did.
从没办过这样的案子
I never did a case like this.
但这还不够
But it's not enough.
我明早就要回车管队了
I gotta go back to Auto tomorrow morning.
我总觉得这事还没完
I just feel like this just ain't finished.
探员
Detective.